|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Alchemy
Shower
This is the clothing of the magicians of Jeonjingak
You will increase your dignity as a magician of Jeongjingak
Be successful in learning spells
This is the amulet of the magicians of Jeonjingak
He grants the right
step everywhere in Sosnovy Bor and Jeonjingak
This is a set of rules
Will you follow him
And if you break the rules, you will be punished accordingly
Chan Wook, stand up and bow to the head
Chan Wook, turn around
and bow to the rest of the magicians
From now on, Chan Wook, the eldest son of the Chan family,
magician of Jeonjingak
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee
Hey Chan Wook
- Congratulations
- Congratulations!
-You've come a long way
- Yes, yes, yes, guys.
Today we will hold a celebration in honor of our new magician - Chan Wook
We are waiting for everyone in Chwiseonru
The Chan family has already paid
food and drink in Jwiseonru
Therefore
everyone should drink until they drop
Chwisonru!
- Chwisonru!
- Chan Wook!
I remember how Chang Gan came here with little Chan Wook. It's like it was yesterday
I can't believe this day has come
I can't believe it myself
Here
Eat
What is this?
Goveniya pill
Eat before you drink
Children will drink until the last moment
We must at least try to keep up with them
I won't get drunk without it
I should think about my age
What about my age?
So there are gray locks
It seems to you because of the sunlight
Look at him
Look how silky my hair is
So beautiful
I'll keep this to myself
Yes, take it
Lady Do Hwa,
young master
became a magician of Jeonjingak like his father
Are you happy?
You did a great job
since we met
I understood at first sight
You are my master
Nak Soo
I want you to become my teacher
What nonsense?
If you survive
I will become your master
Master
I finally got it
Moo Deok
So how? Does it suit me?
How to say... How should I know?
Teacher, what does your student look like?
These clothes suit Yulyu and Park Dan Gu,
but on my student it looks just perfect
Enough is enough
I can't breathe
teacher,
thank you
Okay, Moo Deok. Let's go have a drink
Chan Wook, wait
- Chan Wook...
- Mister, you look so good
Owner
Accept it
Master Huo gave you a govenia pill
Oh, goveniya?
We must divide
It's perfect for hangovers
Here, maid Kim
Maid Kim
I was going to give it to you. True
Maid Kim, come back. Take it. Well really
Maid Kim please
Born under the king's star entered Sosnovy Bor
His father used an ice stone to cast spells
The birth of Chan Wook is the result of this witchcraft
This child is a disaster for Sosnovy Bor
Why do you think Chang Gang did this?
He could make his son king
use the stone to possess Hwansu. He would subjugate the world to himself
Why did he seal his son's gate?
and hid the ice stone?
Because I was weak
He sealed everything and ran away
because he couldn't handle it
Do you think Kil Joo
killed Chang Gang?
If he came back...
Chang Gang wouldn't do something like that openly
I suspect Master Li
We need to gain more strength before the Pine Forest begins to climb
Ten years ago we successfully
got the stone sealed by Chang Gan
You found him
Boo Young,
give me the ice stone
She was so young, but she was able to find the stone
It must be admitted that her powers were truly amazing.
I heard that Jin Ho Kyung doesn't believe in his daughter's death
and is still looking for her
That's why I want to find her
I will find the daughter she has been looking for for so long.
and make Jin Ho Kyung my puppet
How do you find a dead girl?
I'll find someone
The one who will make Ho Kyung believe that it is Boo Young
Here. Eat
Have you eaten anything since you left Sari Village?
Here
Eat
Take your time
Why is this blind girl sailing alone to the city?
She's looking for a friend
Her friend stole all her things
and fled to the city
Poor girl
Do you know where to go? What's your friend's name?
Moo Deok
My friend's name is Moo Deok
- "Moo Dok"?
- How will she find her?
Sweet toffees!
- Sweet toffees!
- Try our cookies!
Come here! Buy!
Sweet pies!
The weather is nice, isn't it?
Mom, buy a pie
I have no money
Mom, buy it!
Well, what are you doing?
Okay, wait
Oh, where are they?
- Where is my money?
- What's happened?
The money is missing
- What should I do?
- My ring...
- I lost the ring!
- Heaven...
What?
This is all?
The ring is also cheap
I crucified myself there and it was all in vain
- Thank you
- Pour it for me
- Have a nice one
- Thank you
You knew who I was all along
Instead of a friend nearby, you have a whistle
It means your friend left you
Mr. Yul?
Ah, Moo Deok
Why are you sitting on the street?
Won't you drink?
No. I've had enough
I'm already drunk
And you look good
I'm drunk
so I got lost
I get lost quickly if my head is foggy
How can you get lost here?
Get up, I'll take you home
You got hurt
It's dangerous
Are you scolding me again? Maybe not today?
It's not for me to scold you
I made a mistake myself
Are you?
Yes
I've always done the right thing. Didn't go astray
But I'm lost
And now I'm holding your hand
I don't know where my path will take me
He will lead you with me
Are you holding my hand?
Let's go
You get lost when your head is foggy
All because you think about a lot
When this happens, think about one thing
For example, think about me now
Okay. Now I'll think about you
Mr. So, can I ask you something?
What's happened?
You said that you dreamed of me
What did my vision tell you?
that you like me
- What?
- What is it?
You repeated this yourself often
Well, that's because...
Was it all a lie?
I like you, but...
Yes I like you
My gratitude
Did he really believe it?
I hope not
Enough is enough
All thanks to you, master
I'm sure Ms. Do Hwa would be happy
Finally I...
I feel like I did something good for Do Hwa as an apology
You didn't do anything wrong
I was the one who brought her to Sejukwon from my hometown.
That's how she met Chang Gang
Do Hwa was so kind
I can't believe he believed all this gossip
Chang Gan, such a scoundrel
Master, you're drunk
It's your fault!
What did I do?
I brought Do Hwa to Saejukwon to set you up with her.
So what?
Holy heavens
With such looks and skills
can't win a girl's heart?
How annoying you are!
Well, yes
Master Huo helped you so much,
and you didn’t take advantage of a single opportunity
I did
everything I could
I wrote poetry
Gave gifts
But you didn't confess to her
"I love you"
"Will you be mine?"
Beat around the bush, but didn't say anything
Of course, you lost to the one who said everything straight
Is it necessary to talk openly about feelings?
Enough hints
How annoying are you?
They showed interest, but they kept their distance
Then they approached again
You need to tell a woman about your feelings
This way she can decide whether to wait for you or not.
If love is so fickle only because it has not been expressed out loud,
then I don't need her!
If a woman decides to leave me and go with someone else,
so be it
"So be it..."
Continue without me
Where are you going?
I'm leaving
Maid Kim
Stay. Have a drink with us...
Stay...
Maid Kim, come back, okay?
- I'll wait
- Well...
- Maid Kim
- Someday he will regret it
Maid Kim!
So this is where people drink
Everyone is waiting for you. Come in
I can't drink
I'm out of tea. We must return to Danhyangok
Get me some food
Okay
The smell of women's perfume and the smell of booze
This is not the place for me
Loves
Doesn't like
Doesn't like it. Loves. Doesn't like...
What am I even doing?
Forget it
Mommies! What to do now?
Exactly
You are a magician, right?
Master Li?
Are you Master Li?
I am a maid of the Chan family. Serving Mr. Chan
Thank you
Not worth it
I guess it got hooked when you caught me
Wait, let me
Sorry
Done
I've been waiting for you all evening
to thank
Like this
Where did he go?
Master Li?
Is it because I haven't had tea for a long time?
Saejukwon
Master Huo is not here right now
But he was waiting for your arrival
Come on in
Celebration for the new magician Jeongjingak?
Master Huo will return drunk
Everyone knows how grandpa likes to drink
Madam, maybe we can go to Chwisonra?
Your future husband will be there
- What?
- Madam Huo told me everything
I heard that your grandfather chose several magicians to be your husbands
Among them is Pak Dan Gu from Sosnovy Bor
and Seo Yul from the Seo family
I'm not here for marriage
I will help in the royal hospital
Do you think the Crown Prince is on the list too?
- Your beauty...
- Song Yi!
Your reasoning has already disgraced me once
Have you forgotten already?
Are you talking about that arrogant magician?
I had to ask the name to tell Master Ho
Exactly
I should have asked the name
Are you okay?
I wonder if I'll see...
him again
Enough is enough
Uk, you owe me
so promise
- Promise what?
- One day,
when I ask you to do something, you will do it
Okay, I promise
Wait a minute
First I have to clarify something
I'm asking because you know Master Li
Have you drunk his chastity tea?
No. Never. Never drank
So you're not celibate?
Of course not. I want to get married someday
Wonderful. Here
You are now also a candidate
You three are candidates
Don't forget to thank Master Li
If he hadn't vouched for you, there would have been problems.
Of course
You've already cast doubt on people by showing Tansu
which was owned by Nak Su
Wook even wanted to become Nak Soo's student
What are you talking about?
What?
He was upset that no one could open his gates,
that's why I joked like that
Are you true
did he say that?
Yes, it's true
Yul, tell them
what is the punishment for magicians who are addicted to dark magic?
You can lose all your energy
not being able to cast spells
Then they will be expelled from Deho,
and descendants will never be able to become magicians
Remember this
Don't ever say that again
Why is dark magic bad?
What?
Regular spells kill people too
And dark magic can sometimes save lives
How to separate one from the other,
you need to think about human intentions, this is more important
So you would use this magic
what if it saves someone's life?
If this magic saves someone,
I don't see any problem
Puppy! How dare you!
You are the magician of Jeongjingak
How dare you say that you would use this magic?
If you're going to act like this,
give back the energy I gave you
- Chapter
- What is it?
The Crown Prince is heading here to meet Chan Wook
Your Highness
Hello
Crown Prince! Say hello to him!
Came here after hearing about the celebration
But it seems I ruined it
Come to think of it, it's all thanks to me
I must be an honored guest
Why did the mood deteriorate so much?
I'm sure deep down
you were hoping it would be my funeral and not a holiday
So the only thing I can do is
greet you calmly
Funeral or holiday
there's always booze there
So I took some with me
Will there be another fight?
Chief, you should come down
Let's wait and see
To congratulate Chang Wook on his victory,
I'll pour him a drink
You mastered Ryusu and became the magician of Jeongjingak
in less than two months
Congratulations
I lost the fight, but...
I'm glad as the Crown Prince
Deho is such a good magician
It's worth celebrating
Have a drink
and become the best magician in the country
Make Daeho proud of you
Chan Wook
Thank you Your Highness
I'll pour you some too
I hope you become a wonderful king
Become a great king, Your Highness
That's good
The Crown Prince holds no grudges
Prince, heir to the throne,
and a young man born under the king's star
Two of Jinyeowon's relics are broken
They have no energy, they are useless
Burn them and scatter the ashes over Lake Gyeongjeongdaeho
Yes, mother
Madam, the master is back
Father?
Cho Young
wife
Father!
My Cho Young
Let me take a look. You have become even more beautiful
I'm back
I found her on Volcano Island in the south
She lost her parents as a child
so he doesn’t remember anything about them
She seems to be the same age as Boo Young
Do you have any left?
something from childhood?
Unlike Boo Young, she has no energy,
and she can't cast spells
She may have lost her strength while away from Jinyeowon.
But if she really is a member of the Jin family,
her strength will easily return
This door will show us
are you really a member of our family
Am I not the daughter you have been looking for for a long time?
No, apparently
But thank you for coming this far. They'll give you enough money to get you back.
Do you think mom will be angry because of another disappointment?
What should I do, father?
Mother
The bird in the cage died
You're right. Poor
Until yesterday I felt warm energy
And now nothing
I can see, but you still noticed first
Every living thing has energy
Through this energy I see the world
Boo Young, may you not see what others see
You are special and you see what others simply cannot see.
You made me a new blindfold
I want to try it on
wife
Don't be upset
I didn't expect much when I brought her here.
So you brought just anyone?
So you're just trying to please me
That's why we haven't been able to find her for 10 years.
I...
I'll start searching again
Forget it
Jin Moo from Jeonbugwan will help find her
I thought you hated your stepbrother
I hate it. But if we're talking about Boo Young,
I'm ready to resort to his help
Get out
I'm looking for someone here
Moo Deok is here right?
There are a lot of people here now, come back tomorrow
Pushing me
Do you know who I am?
And who?
I am a magician of one of the supreme families of this country
Show you my magic?
Consider yourself lucky
If I put energy in my hand, you would die
Sorry. I'm sorry
It's just a gisaeng house. Do you not allow visitors?
Today is the festival of the magicians of Jeongjingak
- Pine forest?
- Yes
Even the Crown Prince is here
I heard she was sold to the biggest gisaeng house in Daeho
This must be the house
If you give me your name, I'll introduce you
Not worth it. I'll be back tomorrow
What is it?
Who was there?
She said she's from a high family
I think it's Jinyoewon
She had something on her neck with the Jinyaewon crest on it.
Jinyoewon?
Their magicians are always rude and picky
Are you okay?
It doesn't hurt. She's weak for a mage
What if she lied and the coat of arms is just a fake?
If in Daeho you pretended to be someone from the supreme family,
you can die
Strange girl
In Deho Fortress, magicians actually have many privileges.
Moo Deok must be out there somewhere
We need to live off her money at least a little
If I say that I came to return it,
I'm sure she'll let me stay, she's kind
- Hey, who are you?
- Scared
Wait for me outside
Yes, Your Highness
She must come out
One, two, three
Four, five...
Your Highness
Your Highness!
I was touched once again
your endless generosity
Yes, I pretended to be kind and generous
Might turn this place upside down
But, as I already said, I don’t want magicians to become my enemies.
What? Do you think I'm stupid?
You acted very wisely and intelligently,
hiding your pettiness and emotions
I decided to show pettiness only to you, Won Moo Deok
I can imagine how hard it was to pour him a drink,
when you would like to poison
That's why I rushed here as fast as I could
I hate your master to the point of nausea
Of course
My liver is burning with hatred for him.
I have no doubt
And you... you support him...
I don't like you either
My generosity was intended for you, not for him.
Won Moo Deok
If you get into a fight or quarrel between us again,
I'll kill you first
Your Highness, if I am to die by your sword,
I won't hold a grudge against you
Will you serve the master anyway?
What a faithful servant
Maybe we should build a monument to you?
I am so honored to receive your recognition.
Forget it. Disappear
Until I lost all my generosity and became petty again
- Your Highness
- What? What again?
Did you have a dying wish?
How are your wounds? Are you okay?
I should have asked earlier
Don't worry. The attack was not strong
And Ho Yeom has already patched me up
You were taken by surprise because you did not expect this from my master
But you, of course, are stronger than him
Naturally. Who knew he was using Tansu?
Fraudster
Oh, you’re talking about that sachet,
which she hung by the latrine pit to ward off flies?
Where is the sachet I gave you?
And what?
Suddenly you hung it by the latrine pit to ward off flies
Here
Why hang such a treasure near the latrine?
Exactly. I knew you wouldn't do it
Well, okay
Have a nice trip, Your Highness
- That's enough
- That's right
- Owner
- Leave me alone
Wake up, master
- Hey
- Just look
He won't sober up until tomorrow morning
Gets drunk quickly
He drank everything the Crown Prince offered him.
We should have helped him then. You're the only sober one here
I was busy, I was singing
Place the palanquin
Only those who are allowed can pass here
If you are not from Sosnovy Bor, leave
You can't either
I'm Moo Deok
Master Chan's maid
You know
You were only allowed in because Chang Wook was a guest here before.
But now everything is different
He is a member of Sosnovy Bor, and you are not
That's why you can't
What will happen to the owner?
He's very drunk. I have to take care of him
Jeongjingak's servants will take care of him
No!
I need to be close to the owner
Let me in
Let her in already
Uk will do something if she's not around
No Jeongjingak magician has the privilege of his own maid.
Chan Wook entered Pine Forest, so he must follow our rules
So I really can't get in?
These are the rules
Go home for now
I'll bring Wook home when he wakes up
Chan Wook can't leave
He cannot leave Sosnovy Bor until he completes his studies.
This is also a rule
Exactly. We stayed here too
That is,
I can't get in and my master can't get out?
And we can't be together?
Once I understand, go home with them
Wait...
It's Chang Wook's first day in Jeonjingak
Do you want him to break the rules on his first day?
Let me in!
If you stand there, she won't leave
If the head finds out, I'll punish her
So let's go
Moo Deok, go home. We'll find a way
Master!
Take me with you!
Grandpa, how have you been?
Everything is fine
You have grown into a beautiful girl
Master Huo, one drunken magician was delivered
because of his heavy breathing
He's just drunk, take care of him yourself
This is Chan Wook. You gave him your energy
What? Chan Wook?
Uk?
This is that magician
Yoon Ok, come here
Okay
His energy gates have been closed for many years, and I opened them for him
I even gave him my energy. His name is Chan Wook
Chan Wook?
Yes. Only a month has passed and he has already mastered Ryusu
He's a genius
In a month?
Truly a genius
Well I'm very drunk
I'll go to my room and go to bed
Take care of him
Come on
Okay grandpa
We met again
Mr. Chan Wook
I didn't come all this way to give up.
I'll get inside by any means necessary
Moo Deok
Your master is dying. My head is spinning
Chan Wook,
if you leave me
I swear I'll kill you
Mr. Yul?
I thought maybe you were still here
And I turned out to be right
I won't leave for anything
I should be with the owner
Sitting here won't solve the problem.
Just make Uka break the rules
Then all his efforts will be in vain
You're right
Go home, wait there
I'll accompany you
Tell my master
that I will find a way
get to Sosnovy Bor to the owner
Tell him to hold out until then
Fine. I'll tell you
My head hurts so much
It's all the prince
Moo Deok
- Bring some water
-Who is Moo Deok?
Who are you?
Don't remember? We met at the inn
Don't lie
You were staring at her the whole time!
Ah, Ta Sun is saying something
Exactly, Soon Yi
Why are you here?
Lady Ho is the granddaughter of Master Ho Yeom
I see
Is that all?
If she tells Master Huo,
how rude you were to her, the master will be angry with you
He never liked me anyway
Let him tell
Well, at least thank her
Mistress took care of you all night
Your lady?
It's better not to mention this to her.
Have you met Uk yet?
Yes
Chan Wook helped Yoon Ok when she was in trouble
I see
Uk isn't the type to just help people.
What are you talking about him?
I heard you came from Vol Fortress
Me and the gentleman's mother are from there.
- I see
- Perhaps that's why
you remind me of Mrs. Do Hwa
I think you and my master are destined to be together
If people from the same city should be similar,
then you should also be similar to each other
But you have nothing in common
I don't understand what you're talking about
Maid Kim, you are great,
but sometimes you exaggerate and make hasty conclusions
Are you saying I'm lying?
I didn't say that
Here and now
They got upset and even called themselves a liar
Yes, yes, of course
I'm an easy to get upset liar
When did I call you a liar?
Now that's exactly what you said
Those were your words
- What's wrong with you?
- It's your fault...
What kind of relationship do they have?
They have a strange and peculiar relationship,
tied to affection
- You were the first to be upset
- You said I was lying
They seem close, but there's nothing special there
- You yourself sat here, repeated...
- But you see,
- he's too stupid
- Keep calling me a liar
And it's annoying
There are no words
We have evidence and witnesses
Witnesses? How annoying you are!
How did you and Uk meet?
- Well...
- Madam
Sorry for interfering
Can we talk?
Of course
You can talk here
This is personal!
Let's go
What's going on with them?
The gentleman seems very serious
That's it
Judging by the way Yoon Ok follows,
there is something between them
- What is this?
- Who knows?
I'll follow them and find out
Sit down immediately!
He sat down now!
But this is interesting to you
How can you be so slow-witted?
He's hopeless
It's like an incurable disease
Sit down
Why do they always scold me?
What's happened?
Have you already told everyone about what happened that day?
I was uncomfortable with you following me
and it’s also rude of you
The beauty was not impressive
And I didn't follow you
No
I wouldn't mention something so shameful
You don't think I'm cute
My beauty did not impress you and you did not follow me
I'm embarrassed to even think about it
So I will remain silent
I have
there is common sense
No, that's not what I'm talking about
I'm talking about the soul swallower
The soul swallower who tried to kill you
So it really was a soul swallower?
Yes. But you can't talk about it
Do me a favor. Keep it a secret
You saved my life, I will fulfill your request
Thank you
Since we share a secret, we should at least introduce ourselves
I am Ho Yoon Ok
I'm Chan Wook
I know. I've heard a lot
Me too. This old man...
That is...
Master Huo always boasted about his granddaughter
Did grandpa tell you something about me?
You will be embarrassed
Really...
he walked and repeated that his granddaughter
"beautiful, like a beautiful fairy." No, right?
Yes, he told everyone that you dazzle with beauty
Not me, unfortunately
It's really awkward
I can't believe it...
This old man...
That is, Master Huo shows such affection
He said the same thing about my mom
They told me I look like your mother
I think this is what fairies look like to grandpa
What?
Doesn't look like it?
I don't know
I've never seen her
And how would I meet a fairy?
It's hard to say
Have you sobered up?
Yes. Heard you were around all night
Yes
I thought it was Moo Deok. Sorry
I made tea with herbs
I hoped he would drink
Saejukwon
Wait a minute
Have you seen Moo Deok?
She came with me yesterday, but she's nowhere to be found
She went home
Why did she leave without me?
Did you leave your drunken owner and go home?
Now the servants of Sosnovy Bor will take care of you
Moo Deok doesn't belong to us, she can't come here
Wait...
Moo Deok thought
she can follow Uk to Sosnovy Bor
I'm sure she imagined seeing you every day.
Probably upset
Yes. Hope she's ok
Apparently, Uk found out
He's probably going to see his uncle
Uncle won't allow this
No magician had a personal maid
And you are no exception
Why?
You, as an exception, kicked me out of here 20 years ago
Why not make one more exception?
All because Tansu taught you
outside these walls?
You need Moo Deok
to keep in touch with the teacher?
Master Li has already confirmed that I trained myself
He saved you, but people are still gossiping
Some even think
what your father taught you, Chang Gan
At first people said that I was not his son
Now they are saying that my father taught me?
When exceptions happen, people start chatting
You quickly mastered Ryusu and used Tansu
This is too unusual
You...
trying to get attention
making people talk about themselves?
The head can't be allowed to suspect Moo Deok.
Otherwise he will find out that she is a nomad
Okay, I understand that you are against it
So will you just follow the rules?
Yes
It took me so long to get here
I can't risk it for some maid
I want to buy a spirit amulet on the black market
Find me one
How can you ask for such a thing when one was killed because of an amulet?
If they catch you, they will kill you too
I should be next to him. The owner needs me
Not at all. He doesn't need you anymore
He needed you when he ran away alone and trained.
And now he's in Jeongjingak
There are plenty of other servants there
The magicians of Sosnovy Bor will also help him
There's nothing more you can do for him
Why does he need you?
The head entrusted me to teach you the basics
I'm honored to be your teacher
I rely on you
This is the Jeongjingak rulebook
From these books you will learn about the virtues of magicians, as well as all the prohibitions
You can't
leave this place until you learn everything
Yes. I'll follow the rules
You can start
read
Mister
Maid Kim
How did you get in?
I thought you were closed again
in the secret room for disobedience to the head
But here you are in the study hall
I'm proud of you
Maid Kim, you can be proud of yourself
You raised this gentleman well
It is worth noting that the tables are low
And the chairs are uncomfortable
I'm taller than the rest
and I'm uncomfortable
But there's nothing to be done, these are the rules
What is your relationship with Ms. Huo?
What did you talk to her about?
Nothing special
I need to read all these books. It's time for you, maid Kim
Do you need some ink before class?
No, I have to do everything myself
These are the rules
Rules. I see
Okay
I'll go. See you later
Maid Kim,
take care of Moo Deok. She's probably worried
Why should she worry if you are completely fine?
I think she's happy
She suffered so much because of you
You're a picky eater, she had to cook three times,
when she was with you in the mountains. Carrying water for bathing
Wash your clothes. Do you know how much work this is?
Moo Deok really suffered
I'll take her to see flowers and buy her something tasty.
I'll take care of her
She will be calm if you are not around
Do you think so?
Chan Wook has already reached his goal
Maybe he really doesn't need me anymore
He left 12 teachers
It was necessary to poison him and find something to blackmail him with
I trusted him too much
Moo Dok!
Moo Deok
Do you have an amulet?
I can't do this. But now you can pass the exam
Do you want me to take the magician exam?
Are you crazy? Don't talk nonsense
Sosnovy Bor conducts an exam not for magicians
They even have a competition there because of the fierce competition
Competition?
We hire servants in Sosnovy Bor
So they just hire servants
Moo Deok, you are the servant
Yes, I know. But I'm no ordinary maid
I refuse
Why be angry?
Do you know how hard it is to get there?
Moo Deok, you look tired
Eat before you leave
Maid Kim
Are you from Sosnovy Bor? Have you seen the owner?
Yes. I saw it. He's fine
What does he want me to do now?
When will he come for me?
He wants you to live well here
Admired the flowers, ate sweets
Did he say admire the flowers and eat sweets?
Yes
Didn't he say when he would come to meet me?
According to the rules, he cannot go out
He's determined to follow the rules
I don't worry about him anymore
I think Uku doesn’t need me around anymore
Moo Deok,
and you don’t know who our master likes?
Maybe this is the girl I saw in Sosnovy Bor
Girl? Is he dating someone?
Well he told me
that his heart belongs to a girl,
which is like a bird's egg on the top of a tree
And also that she has no one but him
I can imagine how he worries and cares about her
When a man takes care of a woman, what do you think that means?
It means he's in love
But it's me
There were bird eggs
Teacher, let's remain devoted to each other
I almost died thanks to you
my crazy master
Our teacher-student relationship will last until you become the best,
to help me get my energy back
When I regain my strength and become Nak Soo again,
we will no longer be teacher and student
May I know why?
Because then you won't have any reason to protect me anymore.
And I won't have a reason
be lenient with you
Teacher! It's me, Chan Wook
So what should we do?
Everything is bad
Moo Deok
I miss you
Thanks for watching with us!
doramamania
Alchemy
Shower
I'm not going to teach Uka
So you didn't take him under your wing, you just locked him here
Help!
It was definitely Moo Deok!
Why does she always have to be somewhere else?
Master!
Why the letter? As long as it conveys your feelings...
The gentleman is already in love with someone
It's harder than I thought
Your Highness!
She was always by Uk's side
You have to try to read what you can't see
Moo Deok